money4gold.co.uk 2010-12-20

# Money4gold Official Website - The trusted place in the UK to Sell Gold Jewelry and earn Cash

## Privacy Policy

Money4Gold (www.money4gold.co.uk) respects Internet users' concern about the privacy of their personal information. Therefore, we have created this Privacy Policy in order to explain our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by recipients of our marketing messages, visitors to our Web site, and our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties. 

Money4Gold is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organisation whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.money4golduk.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our compliance department by emailing compliance@Money4GoldUK.com or by writing to Money4Gold Compliance at 32 Bloomsbury Street, London, WC1 3QJ. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Collection of Information**  
In general, we may collect personal information from recipients of our marketing campaigns and visitors to our Web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by (1) completing our registration form, (2) electing to use one of our services, or (3) contacting us (including our webmaster, customer service representatives, or other employees) by email or phone. As part of these activities, we may ask individuals to provide us with information including, but not limited to, name, physical address, email address, telephone number, and demographic information. You can request the personal information you have on file with us at any time by emailing compliance@Money4GoldUK.com or by writing to Money4Gold Compliance at 32 Bloomsbury Street, London, WC1 3QJ.

As part of the standard operation of our Web site and the web pages that you access via hyperlinks in our online marketing campaigns ("Other Web Pages"), we may collect certain non-personal information from visitors including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site. In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behaviour, such as the date and time they visit our Web site or Other Web Pages, the areas or pages of our Web site and Other Web Pages that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing our Web site and Other Web Pages, the number of times the visitor returns to our Web site and Other Web Pages, and other click-stream data. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on the hard drives of visitors computers when they access our Web site) to collect this information, which may be combined with visitors' personal information. We may also use cookies for other purposes, including, but not limited to, retrieving information previously provided by recipients of our marketing campaigns and visitors to our Web site and remembering the passwords of visitors' to our Web Site and Other Web pages. 

We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Web site and these cookies may collect consumers' personal information. Visitors to our Web site are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Web site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives.

**Use of Information**    
We may use information collected from recipients of our marketing campaigns, visitors to our Web site, and our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties for any of the following purposes in either the online or offline arena to send individuals information from our company and to deliver targeted display advertisements and offers through online marketing communications, such as emails, banner advertisements, and pop-up advertisements (by matching criteria provided by our advertisers with information collected from our visitors); to contact visitors to our Web site or registered members of our marketing campaigns when necessary; to help address problems with our Web site or marketing services; to administer our Web site; to conduct internal reviews of our Web site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the site); to help us better understand recipients of our marketing campaigns and visitors' use of our Web site; and to protect the security or integrity of our Web site and other web pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns. Non-personal information will be used for these purposes as well as for conducting internal reviews and monitoring of our web site and other web pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns and providing a greater online experience for our visitors.

**Updating Your Personal Information**    
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct or update it by emailing our Customer Support Department at info@money4golduk.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Service Providers  **   
We utilise the services of the Royal Mail when we mail the G-PAK out to you. Your name and postal address will appear on the envelopes that contain correspondence from us.

**Disclosure of Information**    
We may transfer or otherwise disclose information collected from recipients of our marketing campaigns, visitors to our Web site, and our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties to our employees and independent contractors, to our subsidiaries and affiliates, and to our consultants, other business associates, and suppliers, if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us. Disclosure of information may also be necessary to respond to warrants, subpoenas, or other judicial processes to provide information to law enforcement agencies, or to facilitate investigation of matters of public safety, as permitted by law. 

**Security**    
We have implemented certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from recipients of our marketing campaigns, from visitors to our Web site, and from our marketing partners, advertisers, and other third parties. Access to that information is strictly controlled and limited to certain individuals within Money4Gold. As required by the Data Protection Act of 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given to us, to prevent unauthorized access or loss of such information. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of information will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this. For this reason, visitors should consider any electronic communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or other communications) to be non-confidential. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to an individual is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient, or is otherwise accessed and used without our written permission. By participating in our marketing campaigns or visiting our Web site, you assume this risk. 

**Opt-Out Policy**    
We offer visitors to our Web site and recipients of our marketing campaigns the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you have subscribed to our service and wish to stop receiving any future communications from us, please email us at remove@money4golduk.com. These unsubscribe options are also included in email communications that you receive from us (whether sent on our own behalf or on behalf of third parties) Please note that if you wish to stop receiving communications from any of our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties you must communicate with these entities directly. We are unable to process unsubscribe requests for any of our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties.

We take all reasonable measures to ensure that your unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within ten (10) working days of your request.. However, despite these precautions, there is always the chance that after you unsubscribe you may receive additional communications from us that may have resulted from an inadvertent technical or other processing error. If this happens, please notify us of those communications by writing to remove@money4golduk.com and we will take immediate steps to rectify the situation.

**Children**    
Our online marketing campaigns and Web site are not directed to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children.

**Third Party Web Sites**    
Our Web site and Other Web Pages that are accessible through our online marketing campaigns may contain links to other third party web sites (such as those of our advertisers), which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these web sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any web site that you may access through our Web site.

**Unforeseen Circumstances  **   
In the event that Money4Gold or any of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information acquired by us may be one of the assets transferred.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**    
There may be times when we need to amend, modify, remove, or change various aspects of this Privacy Policy, and we reserve the right to do so at our discretion. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices. Additionally, we will prominently note on our website that our Privacy Policy has been changed and provided you did not elect to no longer receive correspondence from us, you will be notified via e-mail that changes have been made to our Privacy Policy. You can be assured that any changes that we make will not be applied retrospectively and that we will not materially change how we handle previously collected information without your consent. Your continued use of our services following any changes signifies your acceptance of these changes. 

**I further agree to the below statement:  **   
Even if I am on a National DO NOT CALL List, by requesting information and contact as offered on this inquiry form and submitting my contact information which may include my telephone number, you or your assignee are authorised to contact me by telephone at that number regarding Money4Gold for the three (3) month period following date of this consent. 

Money4Gold  
32 Bloomsbury Street  
London  
WC1 3QJ

Last Updated: 3/3/2010
